pagevamp.com 2013-10-27

# Privacy Policy | Pagevamp

Pagevamp may collect personal information from users who use and sign up to the Service. The personal information that we collect includes names, street addresses, phone numbers and email addresses. The Site may also use google analytics and cookies to recognize visitors to [http://pagevamp.com](http://pagevamp.com/) for us to analyze general user traffic patterns. (See IP address below for more info) 

If you sign up for Pagevamp full account, we require your billing information in order to process the transaction. We will retain the last 4 digits of your credit card number and credit card type, so that you may identify the card in the future. We do not store any billing information. The information is discarded after your transaction has been processed and accepted. Your subscription’s default setup will be auto-renewing, as a result a recurring subscription will be created at our payment gateway, Stripe. Stripe will store your billing information on their secure payment gateway for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription. Should you cancel your subscription, your billing information will be immediately removed by Stripe. For more information on Stripe’s terms of services, visit <https://stripe.com/us/terms>. All transactions are processed over an industry standard SSL/TLS connection. 

Pagevamp occasionally obtains IP addresses from users depending upon how you access our web sites. IP addresses, browser and session information may be used for various purposes, including to: 

  * Diagnose and prevent service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * Estimate the total number of users visiting Pagevamp’'s web sites from specific geographical regions.
  * Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content, services or resources that we offer.
  * Monitor and prevent fraud and abuse.

4\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

Pagevamp may revise, modify or update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your particular Pagevamp account or by placing a prominent notice on our site prior to the change becoming effective. 

Our Web site includes add-ons that may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. These add-ons are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

If you have a privacy concern regarding PageVamp, or this policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of those sites, products or services, you should write to us by email at [ support@pagevamp.com](mailto:support@pagevamp.com) or by mail at: 

PMB Creative, Inc.   
520 E 88th St   
New York, NY 10128
